看起来暴风雨已经结束了.
It looks like the storm has passed.
纽约客们 昨晚有7英寸的大雪
New Yorkers, a season high, seven inches of rain last night.
某些地区 狂风暴雨
High winds and flooding in some areas
甚至让一些纽约客都困住了
even left some New Yorkers stranded.
城市人员早上还在努力工作
City crews still working this morning.
他们正在试图恢复电力
They're trying to restore power
好消息是 今天应该是阳光明媚的一天
Good news is, today should be sunny
过去的几个星期 无情的天气
Relentless weather these past few weeks.
所以快出去吧 享受太阳
So get out there, enjoy the sun,
去公园吧 去外边去转转
go to the park, get outside if you can,
因为这不会一直像这样持续下去
because it's not gonna last long.
你在干什么, John?
What are you doing, John?
只是看着你
Looking at you.
到这来
Come here.
你还在录像吗？
Are you still filming?
只是个纪念日
Just an anniversary...
已经有一阵子了.
It's been a while.
节哀顺变.
My condolences.
你怎么样了?
How're you holdin' up?
我一直在问自己 为什么是"她"？
I keep asking "Why her?"
世事无常.
There's no rhyme or reason to this life.
人这辈子总会有几天像这样的日子
It's days like today scattered among the rest.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
别责怪你自己
Don't blame yourself.
你到底来着干什么的， Macus?
What are you really doing here, Marcus?
只是关心下老朋友
Just checkin' up on an old friend.
再见 John
Goodbye, John.
John Wick?
是的.
请在这里签字
Sign here, please.
还有笔
And the pen.
不好意思
Sorry.
晚安 谢谢
Here you go. Good night. Thanks.
John 我很抱歉我不能和你在一起
"John, I'm sorry I can't be there for you.
但 你需要某人或物去爱
"But you still need something, someone, to love.
那么就用它来开始吧 那部车并不能算
"So start with this. Because the car doesn't count.
我爱你 John
"I love you, John.
疾病已经纠缠我很久了
"This illness has loomed over us for a long time,
现在我已经找到我的归属 还有你的
"and now that I have found my peace, find yours.
直到那一天 Helen
"Until that day, your best friend, Helen."
嘿
Hey.
Daisy.
当然
Of course.
嘿
Hey.
过来
Come on.
我起来了
I'm up. I'm up...
I'm up. I'm up.
嘿！
Hey!
哦.
对了.
什么?
待会给你找吃的
We'll grab you some kibble later.
真是部好车
Nice ride.
野马.
Boss 429.
70年代的?
She a '70?
69年的.
'69.
哈.
Huh
漂亮的车.
Beautiful car.
谢谢.
Thanks.
多少钱?
How much?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
这车多少钱?
How much for the car?
这车不卖.
She's not for sale.
哦 我爱狗.
Oh, I love dogs.
什么都可以用钱买的 婊子
这个不卖 傻逼
这货以为自己是谁啊？
祝您好运 先生.
You have good day, sir.
好了 进来吧
All right, come on, then.
你怎么样？
How you doin'?
你要走了吗？
You need to go?
车钥匙在哪？
让那条狗安静点
去找钥匙
嗯？
uh-huh?
这儿 找到了
做个好梦 婊子
哟, Aurelio!
Yo，Aureilo!
啊?
Ah?
我要一个新的VIN号码和一些干净证件
I want a new VIN number and some clean papers.
你从哪弄到那部车的
Where'd you get that car?
车在这吗？
Is it here?
之前在这
It was.
我问你从哪弄到这车的？
I asked you where the hell did you get it?
Iosef Tarasov干的
Iosef Tarasov nicked it.
Viggo的儿子
Viggo's son.
是的
Yeah.
好了 快走吧 离开我的车店 快离开
All right, get out of here. Just get out of my shop. Get out right now.
你是不是吓尿了 Aurelio?
Did you just lose your shit, Aurelio?
因为 你是我的小弟
Because we own you.
我刚刚说什么？ 你说什么？
What did you say? What did you say to me?
你是我的小弟
We own you.
我不是你的小弟 小子
You don't own me, punk.
我为你父亲工作 好不好？
I work with your father, all right?
难不成你把那车的主人给杀了？
The owner of that car, did you kill him or what?
没有
No.
我很确定我弄死了他的狗
I sure as hell fucked up his dog.
你弄死了他的狗？这就是你所做的？
You fucked up his dog? That's what you did?
你弄死了他的狗？
You fucked up his dog?
是的
Yeah...
那太疯狂了 哥们
That's crazy shit, man.
啊 看看你 那太棒了
Aw, look at you. That's great.
你会拿着枪到的我车店来 然后用枪指着我
You're gonna come into my shop and you're gonna pull a gun on me.
啊 那好极了 哥们
Ah, that's great, man. Come on!
现在 要么你现在杀了我
Now, either you kill me right now
要么你滚出我的车店
or you get the fuck outta my shop!
Viggo不会喜欢这样的
Viggo is not gonna like this.
你怎么知道Viggo喜欢或不喜欢什么？
How do you know what Viggo likes or doesn't like?
我告诉你一些他会理解的事
I'll tell you somethin' he's gonna understand.
你他妈真有种！老不死的！
You've got a fuckin' pair on you, old man!
我想我们得换个地方了
I guess we'll be takin' our business someplace else.
你要怎么做？
So what are you gonna do?
我要部新车
I need a ride.
请讲
Aurelio speaking.
我听说你打了我的儿子
I heard you struck my son.
是的 我打了
Yes sir, I did.
我能问问 为什么吗？
And may I ask why?
因为他偷了John Wick的车 先生
Yeah. Well, because he stole John Wick's car, sir.
还杀了他的狗
And, uh, killed his dog.
哦
Oh.
Viggo?
什么
Yeah?
他们同意了你的条件
They've agreed to your terms.
我是说 他们也没什么选择的余地
I mean, it's not like you gave them much
对不对？
of a choice anyway, though, right?
恭喜您
Congratulations.
先生
Sir?
你有看到我儿子吗？
Have you seen my son?
玩的开心吗？孩子？
How was your trip, kid?
我们没撒谎是哪个就永远都不会在看到他们了
We won't be hearing from them anytime soon.
永远
Or ever.
衣服不错啊
That's a nice jacket.
谢谢
Thanks. Yeah.
我要离开吗？
Should I go?
Vigoo 请说英语 谢谢
Viggo, English, please. Come on...
呆在这儿 该死的！
Stay, God damn it!
我做了什么？
What did I do?
我只是做了你要我做的
We did what you asked.
没人看到
No one saw shit.
我不是在说 亚特兰大的那件事
I'm not talking about Atlantic City.
那是什么？
What, then?
你是说 Aurelio的那件事？ 我只是偷了部车！
You mean Aurelio's? So I stole a fucking car!
啊 操 Vigoo!
Aw, fuck, Viggo!
好了 我要走了... 你给我呆在这！
Right, I'll go... You stay!
我不是因为你做了什么而生气
It's not what you did, son, that angers me so.
而是你对谁做了
It's who you did it to.
谁啊？他就是个无名小卒！
Who? The fucking nobody!
那个无名小卒是
That fuckin' nobody
John Wick!
is John Wick.
他曾与我们共事
He once was an associate of ours.
我叫他Baba Yago
They call him Baba Yaga.
夜魔？
The Boogeyman?
John不是那个夜魔
Well, John wasn't exactly The Boogeyman.
他是你派去杀夜魔的人
He was the one you sent to kill the fucking Boogeyman.
哦
Oh.
John是一个被
John is a man of focus,
承诺
commitment,
纯粹意志所驱使的人
sheer will.
是你所不了解的
Something you know very little about.
我曾亲眼看到他在酒吧用铅笔杀了3个人
I once saw him kill three men in a bar.
用一枝铅笔
With a pencil.
就用他妈一枝
With a fuckin'...
铅笔
...pencil.
突然有一天他说要金盆洗手了
Then suddenly one day he asked to leave.
当然是为了一个女人
It's over a woman, of course.
所以我和他做了笔交易
So I made a deal with him.
我给了他一个不可能完成的任务
I gave him an impossible task.
一个无人能完成的任务
A job no one could have pulled off.
他那天所埋下的尸体
The bodies he buried that day
成就了我们的今天
laid the foundation of what we are now.
那么 我的儿子
And then, my son,
就在他妻子死了的几天后
a few days after his wife died,
你却偷了他的车
you steal his car
还杀了他的狗
and kill his fuckin' dog.
父亲 我可以搞定这件事
Father, I can make this right.
哦
Oh...
你有什么打算
How do you plan that?
搞定由我所挑起的事
By finishing what I started.
他有听到我说的话了吗？
What the... Did he hear a fucking word I said?
Iosef! Iosef! 听着！
Iosef! Iosef! Listen!
什么？
Huh?
John会过来找你寻仇
John will come for you.
而你什么都做不了
And you will do nothing,
因为你本就一事无成
because you can do nothing.
滚出我的视线！
So get the fuck out of my sight!
你好 John
Hello, John.
我听说了你妻子的事了 我很抱歉
I heard about your wife, and I'm sorry.
节哀顺变
My condolences.
这似乎就是命运 或是偶然
It seems to be fate, or happenstance
或只是纯粹运气不好
or just bad fuckin' luck caused our paths to cross once again.
John?
我们不要被自己不好的天性所驱使
Let us not resort to our baser instincts
让我们像文明人一样来解决这件事
and handle this like civilized men, to move on...
他说了什么
What'd he say?
够了
Enough.
天啊
Oh, God.
准备好人手
Task your crew.
多少人？
How many?
你有多少人？
How many do you have?
晚上好 John
Evenin', John.
晚上好 Jimmy
Evenin', Jimmy.
有邻居抱怨噪音？
Noise complaint?
是的 是噪音
Noise complaint.
你又重新工作了？
You, uh, workin' again?
没有 只是理清点事情
No, just sortin' some stuff out.
啊 好吧
Ah, well...
那就这样吧
I'll leave you be, then.
晚安 John
Good night, John.
晚安 Jimmy
Good night, Jimmy.
我是Wick
This is Wick.
是的 John Wick
Yes, John Wick, that's right.
我想预定个12人份的晚餐
I'd like to make a dinner reservation for 12.
很高兴见到你 John
Good to see you, John.
Charlie.
你气色不错啊
You look good.
我就怕你早就不干这些了
And here I'd feared you'd left all this behind.
我以后还能再接到你电话吗？
Will I be hearin' from you anytime soon?
再见 Carlie
Goodbye, Charlie.
John.
肯定是他干的
Of course he did.
悬赏John Wick
Put a contract on John Wick.
多少钱？
How much?
两百万
Two million.
请说英语 Viggo
English, Viggo, please.
把Iosef放在红圈里 然后我们守株待兔
Put Iosef in the Red Circle and wait.
为了什么？
For what?
当然是为了 John Wick
For John Wick, of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
您登门拜访 有何贵干？
To what do I owe this visit?
我有个工作给你做
I have a job for you.
你怎么不在电话里说
And I've got a phone.
Hmm.
我想要当面给你
I want to offer you this face to face
鉴于你可能觉得这有点私人
seeing as how you might find it personal.
你会为了两百万杀了John Wick吗？
Would you kill John Wick for two million dollars?
毕竟 你是他最亲密的人
After all, you were close.
这悬赏只面向我一人吗？
Is the contract exclusive?
不 面向所有人
No, it's open.
这只是时间问题 得马上解决
It's a timely matter, it has to be handled quickly.
我考虑下
Consider it done.
谢谢 Macus
Thank you, Marcus.
我就知道我能信任你 谢谢那杯酒
I know I can trust you. Thanks for the drink.
918号房 祝您入住愉快
Room 918. Do enjoy your stay.
谢谢
Thanks.
很高心见到你 John
Good seeing you again, John.
Perkins.
您要入住两晚吗
I have you for two nights.
看情况 可能久点
Depending on business, it may be more.
当然 先生
Of course, sir.
这里什么时候装修过了？
So when did the old place get a facelift?
大概在4年前
Around four years ago.
我保证你 先生 这里没多大变化
But I assure you, sir, she really hasn't changed much.
还是同一个主人？
Same owner?
是的
Same owner.
818号房
Room 818.
和往常一样
And, as always,
很荣幸您又入住 Wick先生
it is a pleasure having you with us again, Mr. Wick.
你在干什么 John?
What are you doing, John?
看着你
Looking at you.
到这来
Come here.
你好 Winston
Hello, Winston.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
据我回忆
Now, as I recall,
你是不是就是那个
weren't you the one tasked to dole out
打架从来不输的人?
the beatings, not receive them?
差不多吧
Rusty, I guess.
您有何贵干？
To what do we owe the pleasure?
Iosef Tarasov.
他怎么了
What about him?
我想和他谈谈
I'd like to talk with him.
谈谈 哈
A talk, you say.
我对你这种说辞很熟悉, Johnathon
I'm familiar with the parlance, Jonathan.
我想要问问你
I want to ask you this.
Have you returned to the fold?
只是拜访
Just visiting.
那你有想过吗
Have you thought this through?
彻头彻尾的
I mean, chewed down to the bone?
你躲了一次
You got out once.
你陷的太深了
You dip so much as a pinky back into this pond,
你兴许能找到拜托的方法
you may well find something reaches out
但你只会越陷越深
and drags you back into its depths.
我到哪儿去找他?
嘿.
Wick在大陆酒店里.
欢迎回家, John.
我们有人愿意帮我们摆平他
We have a contact there who's willing to take him out for us.
是吗?
Yeah?
真无耻.
How Bracen.
如果他们敢于破坏酒店的规矩
If they're willing to break the rules of Continental,
双倍悬赏金
double the bounty.
你知道这的规矩的
You know the rules.
别在我这儿做坏事
No business can be conducted on these premises
以避免严重惩罚.
Lest incurring heavy penalties
先喝一杯
Have a drink
然后放松
and relax.
现在
For now.
这是私事
It's personal.
我的天啊! Jonathan!
Holy shit! Jonathan!
嘿, Addy. 我的天啊！
Hey, Addy. My God!
多久没见面了？四年？
How long has it been? Four years?
五年多吧
Five and change.
告诉，在那边的生活怎么样？
So tell me, how was life on the other side?
很好，Addy
It was good, Addy.
比我应有的生活好多了
Far better than I deserved.
嘿 我很抱歉关于你
Hey, I'm sorry to hear about your...
谢谢
Thanks.
我从来没见过你像这样
I've never seen you like this.
像怎么样？
Like what?
憔悴
Vulnerable.
我退休了
I'm retired.
只要你在这喝酒 就代表着你没有
Not if you're drinkin' here, you're not.
还和往常一样？
Usual? Please.
我请客
Compliments of the house.
谢谢
Thanks.
你看到那女孩的胸了吗？
Did you see the tits on that girl?
Lita最好今晚不要工作
Better hope Lita is working tonight.
你是不是怕那啥夜魔了？
Are you scared of the fuckin' boogeyman?
我没有
I'm not.
不，你应该感到害怕
No. But you should be.
我想再喝一杯
I want another bottle!
就现在！给我再弄一杯！
Right fuckin' now! Go get me a bottle!
快点
Come on!
你好 Francis
Hello, Francis.
Wick先生
Mr. Wick.
你是有事而来吗？先生？
Are you here on business, sir?
我恐怕是的. Francis
Afraid so, Francis.
你为什么今晚不休息一下
Why don't you take the night off.
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir.
操你妈！混蛋！
Fuck you, motherfucker!
Isoef在哪？
Where is Iosef?
在楼下的澡堂.
Bath house, downstairs.
快去!
Go!
John Wick在那儿！快去抓他！
John Wick's there. Go get him!
快！他在这儿！他特么就在这儿！他来了！
Move! He's here! He's fucking here! He's there! He's coming!
进去！
Get in! Get in!
快点！
Come on, come on!
晚上好！Wick先生!
Good evening, Mr. Wick.
晚上好！
Good evening.
我能为您效劳吗？
How may I be of service?
医生在吗？
Is the doctor in?
是的 先生 在24/7
Yes, sir. 24/7.
那就让他过来！是的 先生
Then send him up, please. Yes, sir.
你们洗衣服务怎么样？
How good's your laundry?
我很抱歉的说没人会那么好
I'm sorry to say that no one's that good.
我想是的
No. I thought not.
您要喝一杯吗 先生？
May I suggest a drink, sir.
波本威士忌
Bourbon, perhaps.
听起来不错
That sounds perfect.
我的情况怎么样？
So what sort of movement am I looking at?
如果你想要治愈的话
Well, if you're lookin' to heal,
你就得注意点
then keep it marginal.
不过 你要是依然还有
However, if you still have...
事要办的话
...business to attend to,
先用这两个
take two of these beforehand.
要不然的阵线会崩开 你又会流血
Your stitches'll tear and you'll bleed,
但是你还依然可以稳健自如
but you'll have full function.
你需要一些止疼的吗？
Do you need anything for the pain?
不 我能搞定
No, I've got that covered.
嘿 John
Hey, John.
Perkins?
我以为我能进来呢
I thought I'd let myself in.
我注意到了
I noticed.
我还不知道Perkins小姐能从床上下来少过三次呢
I never knew Ms. Perkins to get out of bed for less than three.
Viggo给我四倍的价钱来破坏酒店的规矩
Viggo's giving me four to break hotel rules.
那很蠢 我保证你
That's unwise, I assure you.
你永远都是个娘们
You were always a pussy.
是吗？
Yes?
我很抱歉我现在给你打电话
I apologize for calling you at this hour,
但是我已经收到很多关于
but we have received a number of grievances
你们楼层传来噪音的抱怨
from your floor concerning the noise.
我很抱歉
My apologies.
我在处理一个不速之客
I was dealing with an uninvited guest.
您用什么需要的 尽管吩咐
Have you need then of, say,
晚餐预定 也许？
a dinner reservation, perhaps?
也许. 我会待会打给你
Perhaps. I'll have to get back to you.
不
No!
Iosef在哪？
Where's Iosef?
去你的！
Fuck you.
Viggo在哪？
Where's Viggo?
我才不告诉你呢！
I'm not telling you shit!
你想死在这儿吗？Perkins?
Do you really wanna die here, Perkins?
告诉我
Give me somethin'.
小俄罗斯
Little Russia.
在法庭附近有个教堂
There's a church near Cannon Court.
那里怎么了？
What about it?
那是个前哨战
It's a front.
是Viggo藏东西的地方
It's where Viggo keeps his private stash.
谢谢
Thank you.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
我想是的
I'm thinkin' so.
你好 John
Hey, John.
嘿 Harry
Hey, Harry.
一切安好？
Everything all right?
好着呢
Yeah. Everything's fine.
那我走了
I'll leave you to it, then.
嘿 Harry?
Hey, Harry?
你想赚点钱吗？
You keen on earning a coin?
帮我看管一个睡觉的人？
Babysittin' the sleepin' one?
抓到放掉？
Catch and release?
抓到放掉
Catch and release.
孩子 我该怎么帮你？
My son, how might I help you?
混蛋！
Motherfucker!
让我们去地下室
Let's go to the vault.
打开它！
Open it.
Viggo会杀了我的
Viggo will kill me.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
女士们请出去
Ladies, out.
老实说
Honestly,
你觉得你要怎么解决这些？
what do you think you're going to do with all of that?
这个
This.
别担心
Don't worry.
扫地的会发现你的
Housekeeping will find you.
这样对待女士？
Treat all your ladies like this?
你不是女人 相信我
You are no lady. Trust me.
Harry 是这样吗？
Harry, is it?
你会如何赚到比一金币更多的钱呢？
How'd you like to earn more than just a gold coin?
你破坏了规矩
You've broken the rules.
你在大陆酒店干了坏事
You've done business on Continental grounds.
管理层是不会轻易放过你的
And management does not take kindly to that sort of behavior.
去他的管理层
Fuck management.
别担心 扫地的会发现你的
Don't worry. Housekeeping will find you.
尘归尘
Ashes to ashes.
我能从中恢复过来吗？
Can we recover from this?
Viggo 你知道地下室里面有什么 对吧？
Viggo, you know what was in that vault, right?
什么都没有
It was nothing.
靠！
Shit!
Come on!
我会这么说的 John
I'll say this, John.
他们肯定会搞死你的
They sure as fuck broke the mold with you.
呀
Ay, ay...
你总是如此的
You always had a certain...
...大胆, 你知道吗.
...the audacity, you know.
是吗？哦 是的
Right? Oh, yeah.
我敢说说你还是老样子
I can say you're still very much the John Wick of old.
是吗？
Am I?
人不怎么变化 你知道的
People don't change. You know that.
时间会
Times, they do.
你知道在地下室里有什么吗？
Do you know what was in that vault?
艺术品，钞票，之类的可能没啥价值
Artwork, cash, not without its worth,
但是我在这座城市里的干的坏事的
but the leverage I had on this city,
音频录音，物证,勒索
audio recordings, physical evidence, blackmail,
这些都是无价的！
it was fuckin' priceless!
无价！
Priceless!
是的 我还挺享受这样的
Yeah. I kind of enjoyed that.
我知道
Yeah, I know you did.
是的
Yeah.
你在笑吗？
Are you really laughing?
所以
So...
你结婚了 啊？稳定下来的
Then you got married, ah? Settled down.
你是怎么做到的？
How did you manage that anyways?
运气
Luck, I guess.
是吗
Yeah.
是的 你有你的妻子 我有我的儿子
Yeah, while you had your wife, I had my son.
相信我 你本有个更好的活可做
And believe me, you had a far better deal.
但你却洗手不干了
And then you left.
你退出的样子
And the way you got out,
自欺欺人说过去不会影响将来
lying to yourself that the past held no sway over the future.
但是到最后
But in the end,
我们还是要为我们的恶心做出代价
a lot of us are rewarded for our misdeeds,
这就是为什么上帝带走了你的妻子
which is why God took your wife
然后你摊上了我
and unleashed you upon me.
这回影响你一生
This life follows you.
紧跟着你
It clings to you,
感染每一个与你亲近的人
infecting everyone who comes close to you.
你和我 都被诅咒了
We are cursed, you and I.
这个我同意
On that we agree.
终于达成了共识
Finally, common ground.
好吧
Okay.
站一边去
Step aside.
交出你的儿子
Give me your son.
John Wick.
那只是部车！一条狗
It was just a fucking car! Just a fuckin' dog!
只是条狗
Just a dog...
Viggo?
Yeah.
Helen死了后，我失去了一切
When Helen died, I lost everything.
直到那条狗到了我的门前
Until that dog arrived on my doorstep.
一个来自我妻子最后的礼物
A final gift from my wife.
那一刻 我看到了希望
In that moment, I received some semblance of hope.
一个不在独自一人痛苦的机会
An opportunity to grieve unalone.
但是 你的儿子
And your son
夺走了它！
took that from me!
哦 好了
Oh, come on...
从我身边偷走了它！
Stole that from me!
从我面前杀了它！
Killed that from me!
人们一直在问我是不是重操旧业了
People keep asking if I'm back.
但我不知如何回答
And I haven't really had an answer.
但是现在 我觉得 我回来了！
But now, yeah, I'm thinkin' I'm back!
所以 你要么交出你的儿子
So you can either hand over your son...
要么就在他旁边尖叫着死去
...or you can die screaming alongside him!
冷静 冷静 冷静！
Cool it, cool it, cool it, cool it, cool it!
John
John!
他在哪？Shit
Where is he? Shit.
Shit!
你可以保证我 如果我告诉他在哪
I have your word that if I tell you where he is,
你可以放过我？
you'll let me walk away?
取消悬赏
Pull the contract.
成交
Done.
他藏在一个安全屋， 在布鲁克林
He's kept in a safe house. Brooklyn.
434 华莱士住所
434 Wallace Place.
他们知道你要来的
They know you're coming.
当然
Of course.
但是这已经无关紧要了
But it won't matter.
你能不能别玩那破游戏了？
Will you stop playing the fucking video game?
Will you stop playing that fucking video game?
趴下 趴下！
Get down, get down!
快 快！ 趴下 趴下！
Come on, come on! Get down, get down!
做好安排
Make the arrangements.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的荣幸 先生
Our pleasure, sir.
管理层送来的礼物
A parting gift. From the management.
作为昨晚不幸的补偿
Compensation for last night's unfortunate
事故
incident.
我特么要告诉你多少次？
How many times do I have to save your ass?
谢谢
I appreciate it.
当然
Of course.
你看起来糟透了
You look terrible.
不 我看起来像是退休了
No, I look retired.
退休？
Retired?
你真相信这个？
You really believe that?
你有了新的生活
You made a new life.
但是你还会回到原来的样子
You'll find your way back to it.
是时间回归了
It's time to go home.
不管这是什么 让我们开始吧
Let's get on with this, whatever the fuck this is.
你好 Marcus
Hello, Marcus.
我是John
This is John.
我感谢你能赐我儿子一死
I appreciate you granting my son a swift death.
我也不知道该怎么回复那个
I wouldn't know how to reply to that either.
Marcus背叛了我
Marcus betrayed me.
你取消了悬赏？
You pulled the contract.
只要悬赏还在， 你还有机会
And while it was open, you had every chance,
机会去杀掉John Wick
every opportunity to kill John Wick.
如果你做了工作
And if you had done your job,
我儿子可能还活着呢
my son would be still alive!
为了这么做
And in so doing,
他打破了最主要的规则
he broke the cardinal rule.
谢谢你
Thank you.
Perkins小姐
Ms. Perkins.
为什么我一点也不惊讶呢？
Why am I not surprised?
为了更多的钱
In for a penny, in for a pound.
John 我别无选择
So, John, I had no choice.
我一直很欣赏你 Marcus
I always liked you, Marcus.
最后的老保卫者
The last of the old guard.
哦
Oh.
但不像是其他人 你总是按我的规矩做事
But unlike the others, you go out on my terms.
天啊！不！
God! No!
不 我的天
No, my good sir.
我按自己的意愿办事
I go out on my own.
明白了吗？
See?
演的好！老伙计
Well played, old friend.
结束了吗？Viggo?
We done, Viggo?
结束了
We're done.
好吧 拿着
Okay. Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
给直升机加上油
Yeah. Fuel the chopper.
Perkins 小姐 我对您的致电表示感谢
Ms. Perkins, I apologize for calling you at this hour.
Perkins小姐
Ms. Perkins,
你的大陆酒店的会员资格已经被你自己
your membership to the Continental has been,
废除了
by thine own hand, revoked.
我知道你在想些什么 Jonathan
I know what you're thinking, Jonathan.
我们按暗号行事
We live by a code.
这也是为什么我不是唯一一个告诉你
Which is why I'm not the one telling you that
某人在给在停机坪上的
a certain helicopter at a certain helipad
某个直升飞机加油
is being fueled for a certain someone.
你带了我的香烟了吗？
Have you got my cigarettes?
在这儿
Yeah, I got your cigarettes.
哦 操
Oh, fuck!
对 我们走 快点
Yeah. Super. Come on, let's go. Faster!
直升机就在那儿！ 快点！ 我们走吧！
The helicopter's right down there. Come on! Let's go!
卧槽！
Oh, shit!
该死 我知道他回来
Goddamn, I knew he'd come.
这家伙有什么毛病？
What's fuckin' wrong with this guy?
有人给了他一把枪 谁有枪？
Somebody give me a gun. Who's got a gun?
哦 天啊
Oh, God!
干得漂亮
That was a good one.
谁有枪？
Who's got a gun?
操
Fuck!
Viggo 直升飞机！ 就在那儿！ 我得到那边！
Viggo, the helicopters, right over there. We have to get over there.
啊
Ah!
哦 天啊 我需要一把枪
Oh, my God, I need a gun.
请说英语！
English, please.
好运
Good luck.
俄国死基佬！
Russian cocksucker.
啊
Ah!
操
Fuck!
不！
No!
别用枪了 John
No more guns, John.
别用枪了
No more bullets.
不用就不用
只有你和我 John
Just you and me, John.
你和我
You and me.
发生了什么？John
What happened, John?
我们是职业的 讲准则的
We were professionals. Civilized.
你看我像是有准测的人么？
Do I look civilized to you?
下面见
Be seeing you, John.
对
Yeah.
下面见
Be seeing you.
好了 John 我们回家吧
Come on, John. Let's go home.
好的
It's okay.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.